ladies and gentlemen please welcome
Yvonne car truck the welcome everybody
today
I have the honour and introducing a man
who needs no introduction the his legend
has been built
and his accomplishments are too many to
name
that man is my father the
most people strive their entire lives to
achieve great success
in a single fields my father has
succeeded in many
at the highest level and on a global
scale
he's enjoyed success in a vast diversity
and industries
because the common denominator is him
his vision his brilliance
his passion his work ethic and his
refusal
to take no for an answer the I've
enjoyed the good fortune of working
alongside my father for ten years now
and i've seen these principles in action
daily
I remember him telling me when I was a
little girl
even care if you're gonna be thinking
anyway
you might as well be thinking Bay and
that's how he approaches
any task that he undertakes he thinks
big my father is employed
tens of thousands of people throughout
his career and he is inspired them to do
extraordinary things
he has the strength to make hard
decisions
and motivate those around him to achieve
the impossible
he is an optimist who chases big dreams
and sees potential where others do not
he leads by example and will
out work anyone in any room
my father is
the opposite a politically correct he
says what he means
and he means what he says the
he is also the best negotiator
I have ever met countless times I have
stood by his side
and watch to make deals that seemed
impossible to get done
he has the discernment
understand what the other party needs
and then to get exactly what he wants my
father
knows how to be a fierce opponent but
also
how to be a very loyal friend when it
comes to building bridges
he can do so figuratively but also has
the rare ability
to do so literally on time and under
budget the throughout his career
my father has been repeatedly called
upon by local
and federal government to step in and
save
long-stalled grossly over budget public
projects whether it's building
a skating rink in the heart of Central
Park meticulously restoring
the exterior facade Grand Central
Terminal enabling the development
a new york city is jacob javits
Convention Center
creating a championship public golf
course for the City of New York
or redeveloping the iconic
but totally underutilized all post
office building
on pennsylvania avenue in the heart of
Washington DC
my father succeeds time and time again
where government has failed before him I
consider myself fortunate
to have learned from the best both as an
entrepreneur or
and as a parent my father's a man who is
deeply grounded in tradition
he raise my siblings and me
to work hard and to strive for
excellence
in all that we do he taught us
that we have a responsibility to make a
positive contribution to society
here today my father is again
leading me by example my generation
finds itself at a crossroads
our leadership has been mired
indie rocker C up its own creation if we
don't adapt
politically and economically our country
will be left behind
to address the many challenges we face
we don't need to talk we need action
we need execution we need someone who is
bold and independent
with a proven track record of
successfully creating and building
large and complex and complicated
organizations
and in the process enabling many many
americans to better their lives
I can tell you
that there's no better person than my
father to have in your corner
when you're facing tough opponents or
making hard decisions
he is battle-tested he is a dreamer
but perhaps more importantly he is a
doer
ladies and gentlemen
it is my pleasure to introduce to you
today
unmanned who I have loved and respected
my entire life my father Donald J trump
that is some group for people thousands
so nice thank you very much it's really
nice thank you
it's great to be a trump tower great to
be in our wonderful city new york
and it's an honor to have everybody here
this is beyond
anybody's expectations is been no crowd
like this
and I can tell you sum up the candidates
they winnin
they didn't know the air conditioner
didn't work they sweated like dogs
they didn't know the room was too big
because they didn't have anybody there
how they gonna beat I sis I don't think
it's gonna happen
our country is in serious trouble
we don't have victories
anymore we used to have victories but we
don't have 'em when was the last time
anybody saw %uh speeding let's say China
in a trade deal they kill us
IP China all the time all the time
when did we beat Japan
at anything they send their cars over
by the millions and what do we do
when was the last time use our Chevrolet
in Tokyo
it doesn't exist folks they beat us
all the time when do we beat Mexico
at the border they're laughing at us at
our stupidity and now they're beating us
economically they are not our friend
believe me but they're killing us
economically
the US has become a dumping ground
for everybody else's problems
the
tackle it's true
and these are the best in the finest
when mexico's sends its people they're
not sending their best
they're not sending you they're not
sending you
they're sending people that have lots of
problems
and they're bringing those problems with
us they're bringing drugs
they bring in crime their rapists and
some
I assume a good people but I speak to
border guards
and they tell us what we're getting and
it only makes common sense
it only makes common sense this sending
us
not the right people it's coming from
more than mexico it's coming from all
over south and Latin America and it's
coming
probably probably from the Middle East
but we don't know because we have no
protection
and we have no competence we don't know
what's happening and it's gotta stop
and its gotta stop fast
the
Islamic terrorism is heating up
large portions up the middle east
they become rich i'm in competition with
them
they just built a hotel in Syria can you
believe this
they built a hotel when I have to build
a hotel
I pay interest then I have to pay
interest because they took the oil
that when we left Iraq I said we should
have taken
so now ices has the oil
and what they don't have
haran haz and in nineteen
and I will tell you this and I said it
very strongly
years ago I said
and I love the military and i wanna have
the strongest military
that we've ever had and we need more now
than ever but I said don't
hit iraq because you don't it totally
destabilize the Middle East
a Rand is going to take over the middle
east
Iran and somebody else will get the oil
and it turned out that Iran is now
taking over iraq
they coveted a rant is taking over iraq
and they take it over big way we sped
to trillion dollars in Iraq to drill
your
we lost thousands of lives
thousands in Iraq we have wounded
soldiers who I love I love take great
all over the place thousands and
thousands of wounded soldiers
and we have nothing we can even go there
we have nothing
and every time we give a rack equipment
the first time a bullet goes off in the
air
they leave it last week I read to
thousand 300 hum these
these are big vehicles were left behind
for the enemy
2000 you would say maybe two
maybe four to thousand
300 sophisticated vehicles
there and and the enemy to you're right
the last quarter
it was just announce are gross domestic
product a sign of strength
right but not for us it was
below 0 who ever heard of this it's
never below zero
our labor participation rate was the
worst
since 1978 but they give the GDP below
zero
horrible labor participation rate and
are real
unemployment is anywhere from 18 to 20
percent don't believe the 5.6
don't believe it that's right a lot of
people up there can't get a job
they can't get jobs because there are no
jobs
because China has our jobs and mexico
has our jobs they all other jobs
but the real number the real number
is anywhere from 18 19 and maybe even 21
percent and nobody talks about it
because it's a statistic thats
fallen out sense the
our enemies
are getting stronger and stronger by the
day
and we as a country are getting weaker
even our nuclear arsenal
does it work it came out recently
they have equipment that's thirty years
old they don't even know if it worked
and I thought it was horrible
when it was broadcast on television
because boy does that send signals
to Putin and all the other people
that look at us and they say that is a
group of
people and that is a nation that truly
has no clue take don't know what they're
doing
they don't know what they're doing we
have a disaster
called the big lie Obamacare
Obamacare yesterday came out
that costs are going for people
up 29 39 49
and even 55 percent
and deductibles are through the roof you
have to get hit by a tractor
literally a tractor to use it
because the deductibles are so high it's
virtually useless
it is a disaster and
remember the five billion dollar
website five billion we spent their
website
and to this day it doesn't work a5
billion dollar website I have so many
web sites have all over the place
I hire people they do a website a cost
me three dollars
5 billion dollar
website
where you need somebody
because politicians are all talk no
action
nothing's gonna get done they will not
bring us believe me
to the promise land they will not
as an example I've been on the circuit
making speeches and I hear
my fellow republicans in the wonderful
people
i cum they all want me to support them
they don't know how to bring about the
come up to my office I
a meeting with reaffirming the next week
and they don't know
are you running are you not running
could we have to support
what do we do how do we do it i like 'em
and I hear their speeches and they don't
talk jobs and they don't talk China was
the last time you heard
China is killing us did devaluing their
currency to a level that you wouldn't
believe it makes it
impossible for our companies to compete
impossible they're killing us
but you don't hear that from anybody
else you don't hear it from
anybody else and I watched this features
thank you i watch the speeches are these
people
and they say the Sun will rise
the move will set all sorts of wonderful
things will happen I'll
and people are saying what's going on
I just want a job just get me a job
I don't need the rhetoric I want a job
and that's what's happening and it's
going to get worse because remember
Obamacare really kicks in and 16
2016 Obama is going to be out playing
golf
he might even be on one of my courses I
would invite him I actually would say
I have the best courses in the world
site say you know what if you want see I
have one right next to the white house
right on the potomac if you'd like to
play that's fine
fact I'd love them to leave early and
play that would be a very good
but
Obamacare kicks in in 2016
really big lake it is going to be
amazingly destructive doctors acquitting
I have a friend who is a doctor and he
said to me the other day Donald
I never saw anything like it I have more
accountants
that I have nurses it's a disaster my
patience
are decide themselves they had a plan
that was good they have no plan now
we have to repeal Obamacare and it can
reap
be replayed add it can be replaced with
something much better
for everybody let it be for everybody
but much better and much less expensive
for people
and for the government and we can do it
show
I've watched the politicians I dealt
with them all my life
if you can't make a good deal with the
politician then there's something wrong
with you you're certainly not very good
and that's what we have representing us
they will never make America great
again.
they don't even have a chance they're
controlled
fully they're controlled falling
by the lobbyists by the donors
and by the special interests clearly
thats
the controller pay I have lobbyists I
had to take I have lobbyist can produce
anything for me
a great but you know what it won't
happen
it won't happen because we have to stop
doing things for some people but for
this country it's destroying
country we have to stop and it has to
stop now
now our country needs
our country needs
a truly great leader and we need a truly
great leader now
we need a leader
that wrote the art of the deal we need
a leader that can bring back I jobs can
bring back our manufacturing can bring
back our military take care of our vets
our vets have been abandoned and we also
need
a cheerleader you know when
President Obama was elected I said well
the one thing I think you'll do well I
think he'll be a great cheerleader
for the country I think you'd be a great
spirit
he was vibrant he was your I really
thought that he would be a great
cheerleader
he's not a leader that's true
you're right about that but he wasn't
a cheerleader he's actually a negative
force it's been a negative force
he was a cheerleader he was the opposite
we need somebody
that can take the brand up the United
States
and make it great again it's not great
again
we me we need some body
we need somebody
that literally will take this country
and make it great again we can do that
and I will tell you I love my life
I have a wonderful family they're saying
dead you gonna do something that's going
to be so tough you know all of my life
I've heard
that a truly successful person really
really successful person and even
modestly successful cannot run
for public office just can't happen and
yet that's the kind of mindset
that you need to make this country great
again so
ladies and gentlemen I am officially
running
the
for President of the United States the
and we are going to make
our country great again
it can happen
our country has tremendous potential
we have tremendous people we have people
that
aren't working we people that have no
incentive to work
but they gonna have incentive to work
because the greatest
social program is a job and they'll be
proud and they'll love it
and they'll make much more money than
they would've ever made
and they'll be they'll be doing so well
and we're going to be thriving as a
country
thriving it can happen I will be
the greatest jobs president that God
ever created I tell you the I'll bring
back I jobs from China from Mexico from
Japan
from so many places I'll bring back I
jobs and I'll bring back our money
right now think if this way out China
1.3 trillion dollars we r Japan
more than that so they come in they take
a job they take our money and then
they'll owners back the money
and we pay them in a dress and then the
dollar goes up
so their deals even better how
stupid our own leaders house stupid
are these politicians to allow this to
happen
house stupid art
I'm going to tell you thank you I'm
gonna tell you a couple of stars
about trade because I'm totally against
the trade bill
for a number of reasons number one the
people negotiating
don't have a clue our president doesn't
have a clue
is a bad to go sheer he's the one that
did Bergdahl
we get bad girl they get five killer
terrorists that everybody wanted
over there we get burger we get a
traitor we get a no good trader
and they get the five people that they
wanted for years
and those people and now back to the
battlefield trying to kill us
that's a negotiator we have take a look
at the deal he's making with Iran
he makes that deal Israel maybe won't
exist very long
it's a disaster and we have to protect
Israel
but so we need people on the free trader
but the problem with free trade
is unique really talented people
to negotiate for you if you don't have
talented people if you don't have great
leadership if you don't have people that
know business is not just a political
hack
they got the job because he made a
contribution to a campaign
which is the way all jobs just about a
got free trade is terrible
free trade can be wonderful if you have
smart people but we have people that are
stupid we have people that aren't smart
I we have people that are controlled by
special interests and
it's just not going to work so here's a
coupla stories happen
recently a friend of mine is a great
manufacture
and you know china comes over and a
double their stuff and i buy it i buy
because frankly I have an obligation to
buy because they devalue their
currencies so brilliantly they just did
a recently
and nobody thought they could do it
again but with all our problems with
Russia
with all our problems with everything
everything
they got away with it again and it's a
possible
for our people here to complete so I
won't tell you the story
for two months a great manufacture calls
me up
few weeks ago is very upset
as to what you prop he said you know I'm
a great product I said I know I know
that because i buy the product he said i
cant get it into China
they won't accept it I sent a boat over
and they actually sent it back
they talked about environmental they
talked about also to crap that had
nothing to do with it
I said oh wait a minute that's terrible
does anyone know this he said yet they
do it all the time with other people
I said they sent it back yeah so I
finally got it over there
and they charged me a big para did not
supposed to be doing that
I told them now they do charge a tariff
or trucks
when we send trucks and other things
over there s Boeing
they wanted Boeing secrets they wanted
their patents in all their secrets
before they agreed to buy planes from
Boeing pay
I'm not saying this stupid I'd like
China
I sell apartment 210 I just sold an
apartment for fifteen million dollars
to somebody from China am I supposed to
dislike
I own a big chunk at the Bank of America
building in 1290 Avenue of the Americas
that I got from China in a war 0
very valuable I love China
the biggest bank in the world is from
China
you know where their United States
headquarters is located
in this building in Trump Tower I love
China
people so you don't like China know I
love
but their leaders are much smarter than
our leaders
and we can sustain ourself with that is
too much
it's like it's like take the New England
Patriots and Tom Brady
and have them play your high school
football team
that's the difference between China's
leaders
and our leaders they are ripping us we
are rebuilding China
we're rebuilding many countries China
you go there now
roads bridges schools you
this or anything like it they have
bridges that make the George Washington
Bridge look like small potatoes
and they're all over the place we have
all the cards
but we don't know how to use them we
don't even know that we have the cards
because our leaders
don't understand the game we could turn
off that spigot
by charging them tax until they behave
properly
now they're going militarily they're
building a military Island
in the middle at the South China Sea a
military Island
now our country could never do that
because we have to get environmental
clearance
and the environmentalists would let a
cat we would never build in an ocean
they built in about 1 year this massive
military port
they're building up their military to
appoint
that is very scary you have a problem
with my sis you have a bigger problem
with china
and in my opinion the new China believe
it or not in terms of trade
is mexico so this man tells me about
the manufacturing I say that's a
terrible story I hate to hear
but I have another one Ford so mexico
takes a company car company that was
going to build in Tennessee
rips it out everybody thought the deal
was dead reported in the wall street
journal
recently everybody thought it was a done
deal
it's going in and that's going to be it
going into tennessee great state great
people
all other son at the last moment this
big car manufacture far in
announces they're not going to Tennessee
they gonna spend a billion dollars in
Mexico instead
not good now for denounces
a few weeks ago therefore it is going to
build
82.5 billion dollar
car and dropped and parts
manufacturing plant
in mexico 2.5 billions could be one of
the largest in the world
Fort good company so I announced
that I'm running for president I would
one of the early things I would do
probably before even getting and I
wouldn't even use you know I have I know
the smartest negotiators in the world
I know the good ones I know the bad ones
I know the overrated what you got a lot
of that are overrated
they're not good they think they are
they get good stores has a newspaper's
get buffaloed
but they're not good but I know the best
negotiators in the world and I put 'em
one for each country believe me folks we
will do very very well
very very well but I wouldn't even waste
my time with this one I would call up
the head of or do I know
if I was present
at say congratulations I i understand
that you're building a nice
2.5 billion dollar car factory in mexico
and that you gonna take you guys and
sounded United States zero tax
just flown across the board and you say
to yourself
how does that help us right sign up is
where is a good it's not
so it's a congratulations that's the
good news let me give you the bad news
every car every truck
in every part manufactured in this plant
that comes across the border we're going
to charge you a 35 percent tax
hey and that tax
is going to be paid simultaneously with
the transaction and that said
here's what's gonna happen if it's not
me in the position it's one of these
politicians that we're running against
you know that
400 people that were already and here's
what's gonna happen
did not so stupid they know it's not a
good thing
and they may even be upset by but then
they get to get a call from their donors
or probably from the lobbyist for four
say you can't do that to Fort because
forty
takes care of me and I take a review and
you can't do that to Fort
a guess what no problem taken to build
in Mexico they gonna take away thousands
of jobs it's very bad for us cell
under President Trump here's what
happened the head afford
will call me back I would say within an
hour
after I told them the bad news but it
could be
wanna be cool and you wait till the next
day
you know they want to be a little cool
and I'll say please please please go
back for a little while
and I'll say no interest they'll call
also it's a political people and I'll
say
sorry fellas no interest because I don't
need anybody's money is nice
I don't need anybody's I'm using my own
money
I'm not using the lobbyists are not
using donors I don't care
I'm really rich sure that this by the
way
I'm not even saying that in a bragger
that's the kind of mindset that's a
kinda think it you need for this
country shell because we can make the
country Ridge it sounds crest somebody
should know that's kress
not press we got 18 trillion in debt
we got nothing but problems we get a
military that needs equip it all over
the place
we got nuclear weapons that are obsolete
we've got nothing we got social security
that's going to be destroyed
if somebody like me doesn't bring money
into the country all these other people
want to cut the hell outta
I'm not going to cut it all I'm gonna
bring money in
how we're gonna say but here's what's
gonna happen
after I'm called by 30 friends of mine
who contributed
different campaigns after I'm called by
all the special interests and by the
the donors and by the lobbyists
and they have zero chance a convincing
me 0
I get a call the next day from the head
afford
the state please reconsider all say no
he'll say mister president we decided to
move
the plant back to the United States
we're not going to build and much
check they have no choice they have no
choice
there are hundreds of things like that
a give another example Saudi Arabia
they make a billion dollars
a day a billion dollars a day
I love the saudis many are in this
building they make
a billion dollars a day whenever their
problems we send over the ship's we said
we're going to protect what we doing
began nothing but money if the right
person
ask them they pay a fortune they
wouldn't be there
except for us and believe me you look at
the border with Yemen
you remember Obama a year ago yeah man
was a great victory
red two weeks later the place was
blown-up
everybody get handicapped are equipped
they always keep our equipment
witness it used equipment right there
was keep our equipment
this is a real job because frankly
it would be where to send our surplus
were always losing this gorgeous friend
mister
but look at that border with Saudi
Arabia do you really think
that these people are interested in
Yemen
Saudi Arabia without us
is gone day gone and I'm the one that
made all the right predictions about
iraq
you know all these politicians and I'm
running against
now like it's so nice to say I'm running
as opposed to if I Ron
if I run running
but all these politicians that I'm
running against now
they're trying to disassociate me you
look to push it took him five days
to answer the question on iraqi couldn't
answer the question now
I said is intelligent and I look at
rubia he was unable to answer the
question
is a racket good thing or a bad thing he
didn't know he couldn't answer the
question
how are these people going to lead us
how we couldn't how we gonna go back in
make it great again weekend they don't
have a clue
take it lead us they can't they can't
even answer simple questions
it was terrible but Saudi Arabia is in
big big trouble
now thanks to fracking and other things
the Oilers all over the place and I used
to say it
their ships at sea in this was doing the
worst crisis
that were loaded up with oil and the
cartel
kept the pressure because again
there was smarter than our lives they
were smarter than a lease
there is so much wealth out there that
can make our country so rich again
and therefore make it great again
because we need money
with dying with dying
we need money we have to do it
we need the right people soak
Ford will come back they'll all come
back
and I will say this: this is going to be
an election in my opinion that's based
on
competence somebody said
thank you down
somebody said to me the other day a
reporter very nice reporter
but mister trump you're not a nice
person
that show but actually I am
I think I am a nice person people that
know me like me
does my family like me I think so right
with my fam a proud of my family
by the way speaking to my family Malani
a
barren Chi Donnie
Don Venessa Tiffany
a Bocca did a great job did she do a
great job great the Jared Lara
and Eric I'm very proud of my family
they're great family so
the reporter said to me the other day
but missed a trap
you're not a nice person how can you get
people to
vote for you I said now I said I think
that
number 1 i'ma nice person give a lot of
money away
to charities and other things I think
I'm actually
a very nice person but I said this is
going to be an election
that's based on competence because
people are tired of these nice people
and they're tired of being ripped off by
everybody in the world
and they're tired of spending more money
on education then any nation in the
world per capita
than any nation in the world
and would 26 in the world 25 countries
are better than I said education and
some of them are like third world
countries
but we're becoming a third world country
because of our infrastructure
our airports are roads everything so one
of the things I did and I said you know
what I'll do
%uh do it because a lot of people said
he'll never run number one you want to
give up his lifestyle
to read about that but I'm doing number
two
I'm a private company so nobody knows
what I'm worth and the one thing is that
when you run
you have to announce and certify
to all sorts of governmental authorities
your net worth so I said that's okay
I'm proud of my net with that done an
amazing job I started off
thank you I started off in a small
office with my father in Brooklyn and
Queens
and my father said and I love my father
I learned so much he was a great
negotiator
I learned so much just sitting at his
feet playing with blocks
listening to him negotiate with
subcontractors
but I learned a lot but he's to say
Donald don't go into Manhattan that's
the big leagues
we don't know anything about that don't
do it is it then I gotta go into
Manhattan
I got a bill those big buildings I gotta
do it dead I've gotta do it
and after four or five years in Brooklyn
I ventured into Manhattan and did a lot
a great deals the Grand Hyatt Hotel
I was responsible for the convention
center on the west side I did a lot of
great deals and I didn't
early and young and now a building all
over the world and I love what I'm doing
but they all said a lot of the pundits
on television
well Donald will never run and what are
the main reasons is
his private and he's probably not as
successful
as everybody thinks so I said to myself
you know nobody's ever gonna know unless
I run
because I'm really proud of my success I
really here
I've employed I've employed
hands up thousands a people
over my lifetime that means medical that
means education
that means every so a large accounting
firm in my accountants have been working
for months
because it's big and complex and they
put together
a state financials
is a summary but everything will be
filed eventually with
the government and we don't need
extensions or anything will be filing
right on we don't need any and
it was even reported incorrectly
estimate because they said he had assets
up nine billion says nice a wrong number
that's the wrong number not SS so
they put together this and before I say
I have to say this
I made your fashion which real estate
you notes
list its labor and its unions good and
some bad
and lots of people that are in unions
and its all over the place
and building all over the world and I
have assets
big accounting for while the most highly
respected
nine billion 240
million dollars and I have
liabilities
about 500 thats long-term debt
very low interest rates that one of the
big banks came to me said
Donald you don't have another borrowings
could we loan you four billion dollars
that I don't need it
I don't want it and I been there I don't
want it
but in two seconds they give me whatever
I wanted so I have
a total net worth and now with the
increase it'll be
well over ten billion dollars but here a
total net worth
love eight billion net worth not assets
not liability a net worth
after all dat
after all expenses the greatest asset
Trump Tower 12 ninety Evony the Americas
Bank of America building in San
Francisco
40 Wall Street sometimes referred to
as the Trump building right opposite the
New York's
many other places all over the world so
the
total is eight billion 737
million five hundred and forty thousand
dollars now I'm not doing that
I'm not doing that to Breakers you know
what and at the break I don't have to
believe it or not
I'm doing that this day that that's the
kind
of think Keeney our country needs
we need that think we have the opposite
thinking
we have losers
we have losers we have people that don't
have it we have people that are morally
corrupt
we have people that are selling this
country down the drain
so I put together the statement and the
only reason I'm telling you about it
today
is because we really do
have to get going because if we have
another three or four years you know
where 18 trillion now
we're soon going to be at $20 trillion
according to the economist who are not
big believers in but
nevertheless is what they're saying that
24 trillion we're very close that's the
point
have no return 24 trillion dollars we
will be there soon
that's when we become Greece thats
when we become a country that's on
salvageable and we're gonna be there
very soon we're gonna be there very soon
cell
just to sum up I would do
various things very quickly I would
repeal and replace the big lie Obama
Care
I would build
a great wall and nobody bills was better
than me believe me
and I'll build 'em very inexpensively I
will build a great
great wall on our southern border and I
will have Mexico
pay for that wall mark my words nobody
would be tougher
on ices then donald Trump nope I
I will find within our military
I will find the General Patton
or I will find general macarthur I will
find
the right guy I will find the guy that's
going to take that military
and make it really work nobody nobody
will be pushing us around
I will stop Iran
from getting nuclear weapons
and we will be using a man like
secretary carry that has
absolutely no concept of negotiation
whose make it a horrible it laughable
Dale who's just being tapped a long as
they make
weapons right now and then goes into a
bicycle race at 72 years old
and falls and breaks his leg I will be
doing that and I promise I will never be
in a bicycle race that I can tag
I will immediately terminate a
President Obama's illegal
executive order on immigration
immediately
fully support and backup
the Second Amendment now
very interesting today I heard through
stupidity
in a very very hardcore prison
interestingly name
clinton to vicious murders
to vicious people escaped and nobody
knows where they are
and a woman was on television this
morning
and she said you know mister juppe she
was telling other people like
actually called but she said you know
mister trap
I always was against god's I didn't want
guns
and now since this happened
its up in the prison area my husband and
I
are finally an agreement does he wanted
the guns we now have a gun on every
table
we're ready to start shooting I said
very interesting so
protect the second mm and
and Common Core
Common Core should
it is a disaster Bush is totally in
favor of Common Core
I don't see how he can possibly get the
nomination
he's we got immigration he's in favor of
Common Core
how the hell can you vote for this guy
you just can't do it
we have to end education has to be local
rebuild the country's
infrastructure nobody can do that
like me believe me it will be done on
time
on budget way below cost way below what
anyone ever thought
I look at these roads being built all
over the country
and I say I can build those things to
one-third what they do is
unbelievable how bad you know what
building
on pennsylvania avenue the Old Post
Office were converting it to
one of the world's great hotels could be
the best hotel in Washington DC
we got it from the general services
administration
in washington the O Parma administration
we got it it was the most highly sought
after all one of them but I think the
most highly sought after
project in the history up general
service
we got it people were shocked trumka
I got it for two reasons number one
we're really good number
do we had a really good plan and I lead
in the third
we had a great financial statement
because the general services who were
terrific people by the way
and talented people they wanted to do a
great job and they want to make sure got
built
so we have to rebuild our infrastructure
our bridges our roadways are airports
you come into LaGuardia Airport
it's like we're in a third world country
you look at the patches in the
forty-year-old floor they throw down
asphalt in a truck you look at these
airports we are like a third world
country
and I come in from China and I come in
from Qatar and I come in from
different places and they have the most
incredible airports in the world
you come back to this country and you
have LAX
disaster you have all these disasters
airports we have to rebuild are in for
save medicare medicaid
and social security without cuts have to
do it
get rid of the fraud get whether the
real waste and abuse
but save it people have been paying in
three years
and now many these candidates want to
cut it you save it
by making the United States by make it
as rich again
by taking back all of the money that's
being lost
renegotiate are far in
trade deals reduce our
18 trillion in debt because believe me
were in a bubble we have artificially
low interest rates
we have a stock market that frankly it's
been good to me but I still hate to see
what's happening
we have a stock market that is so
bloated
be careful though the bubble because
what you've seen in the past might be
small potatoes
compared to what happens so be very very
careful and strengthen
our military and take care of our vets
so
so import sadly
the American dream
is dead but if I get elected president
I will bring it back bigger
at better and stronger then ever before
and we will make America
great again thank you thank you very
much